I am Luiphon Sandhalkia Diltz,
third prince of this land
and captain of the knights.
But perhaps most of all...
I am dear Kyros' friend!
Pleased to meet you, sweet Marie!
S-So this is the sort of person he is.
Episode 5 "The Prince and the Pitch-Black Warrior"
You took so long to arrive, Prince Luiphon,
so I was just going to leave with Lady Marie.
I said I was sorry, didn't I? You
can be heartless, darling Mio.
Please don't call me "darling."
Mio.
By the way...
are you hungry?
How does a lavish buffet in
the nobles' salon sound?
Nobles...
I-I'm not very hungry.
Oh, Ilza and Hannah aren't
here anymore. Don't worry.
I'm sorry for recommending them without
knowing their personalities.
No, it isn't that.
The thought of a place as refined
as a salon makes me anxious.
In that case, what about the
swordsmanship exhibition?
I have reserved seats. Let's go and watch!
S-Swordsmanship?
That's right!
I, um, well...
Lady Marie, there's no
need to force yourself.
You hate competitions, don't you?
What?! But why?
This is one of the best aristocratic pastimes!
Yes, please, I'd love to see it!
Now that's the reaction I was hoping for!
I can best any knight with a sword, you know?
Kyros once complimented me by saying, "the
sword is the only place where you show genius."
Then Lord Kyros truly is strong?
He is indeed!
Being complimented by Lord Kyros
made you happy, didn't it?
We will now begin the semi-finals of the
Diltz Kingdom Swordsmanship Exhibition!
This enthusiasm is wonderful, isn't it?
Last year, I fell asleep during the concert.
And dear Kyros kept pinching my cheeks.
Prince Luiphon really loves
Lord Kyros, doesn't he?
I'm having fun just listening to him.
Well, it's enjoyable to discuss
your passions with others.
Now then.
I'm off to procure some food.
What? But we just ate.
I wanted to visit all the stalls.
Your stomach is a separate
dimension, as always.
Go and eat as much as you like.
That fighter in the dark armor
is an impressive warrior.
I see.
Say, are you like this with Kyros, too?
What?
Well...
Well, you're rather
different from the others.
And I've known Kyros a long time.
I heard that the two of you were
in the same year in school.
Yes, and the first time we
met we got into a fistfight!
What?!
As the duke's son, he was just below me in terms of rank at school.
But he said, "Stop judging people based
on their rank, you moronic prince."
M-Moronic?
I thought, "What's his problem?" and
punched him. Then he punched me back.
It turned into quite the commotion.
Does it really warrant that much laughter?
Winner, the pitch-black warrior!
Oh, is it already over?
Yes. By knocking the point of
the blue knight's sword away,
the dark warrior was able to
win with a single strike.
By the look of things, he was holding back.
It seems he has the kindness
to care for his opponents.
My sweet Marie...
doesn't seeing this sort of thing
make you think they're dashing?
Many girls squeal with delight, you know?
I-I...
I don't find being strong in battle
to be particularly wonderful.
Aren't strength and reliability the
things that are most attractive in men?
To be honest, I'm frightened.
I feel like one day that
sword will be pointed at me.
What's that supposed to
mean? You're so negative!
I'm sorry.
Say, Lady Marie Shaderan, why
did you become Kyros' fiancée?
B-Because...
I'm my older sister's replacement.
Yes, I am just a replacement.
And now, we will begin
the championship bout!
The dark warrior versus the green knight!
Begin!
Th-The winner... the dark warrior!
Well, that was an instant defeat.
Congratulations! This is the winner's tro—
He's putting his worry
for his opponent first?
If he's the one fighting, then perhaps even
I might enjoy watching his bouts a little.
My, that is good news.
W-Welcome back.
Spoils of War
I have only just returned.
You mentioned good news?
That dark warrior is the master.
What?
You seem very certain.
His swordsmanship and footwork
are exactly identical to the master's.
Lord Kyros... is the dark warrior?
Shall we see for certain?
Count Kyros Granado, you're so dashing!
Look this way!
Kyros?
Count?
From the Granado Company?
Really?
Lord Kyros! Look over here!
Take off your helmet!
Every male noble in the Kingdom of Diltz
is made to hold the sword at least once.
The master has trained intensively
since he was a child for self-defense.
H-He has?
That was the best expression
I've seen today, thanks.
Prince Luiphon knew from
the start, didn't he?
E-Excuse me. What is this line for?
What? It's the line to make an
appeal to the count of course.
What?
His fiancée apparently died in an accident.
This is a chance to get close to him!
Of course. No one would think that her
incompetent younger sister would replace her.
He may have barbarian blood in him,
but he is the next duke after all.
Indeed! And whomever becomes the duke's wife
can certainly stand proudly in society.
I've heard he's got a difficult
personality, but he's so handsome.
Isn't he?
Barbarian?
Difficult?
Who are they talking about?
Lady Marie?
Excuse me.
Wh-What?
Stop right there!
Just who are you?
Indeed! Who do you think you are?
I am betroth— I am an
associate of the count's!
What?
Lady Marie, I will hold
them here to the last!
Thank you, Mio!
Get out of my way! Who are you?
What was that? They all just
said whatever they liked.
All I did was discover something I liked...
and he's so kind that he
smiled at me so happily.
There's no reason
to ridicule him like that!
Even if there were...
it would only be for drawing
a losing prospect.
What are you thinking?
Why did you tell me to enter
the swordsmanship competition?
You did excellent work! Thanks to
you, it was a rousing success!
That smile is infuriating.
Was it you who exposed my
identity to the crowd?
C-Congratulations on your win!
I've finally begun hallucinating.
U-Um...
Are you the real Marie?! In the flesh?
The one who's like a living miracle?!
Lord Kyros?
I invited her.
What?!
I wanted to show her how
dashing you are, Kyros.
Though, it seems she wasn't
particularly pleased by it.
Marie doesn't like brutality.
Or aristocratic things either.
That's right. And I don't want to
force anyone else's values on her.
Marie's wishes are my only priority.
Well. You certainly seem quite besotted...
but she doesn't seem happy about it.
She's simply replacing her older sister
in a political marriage, isn't she?
You'd have gotten engaged no matter what
kind of man you faced. Isn't that right?
I...
It's true that when I was first
taken to Granado Castle...
I didn't even know what
Lord Kyros looked like.
But...
As I thought, you don't think anything
of Kyros, let alone love him.
Stop attacking her. What
are you so upset about?
When I heard that you were getting
engaged, I was overjoyed.
My dear, obstinate friend, who had turned away
every noblewoman, had finally found his spring.
But in the end...
A political marriage?
And to a woman who is uneasy with
the customs of the nobility,
who sees no merit in your efforts, Kyros?
She's her parents' pawn and—
What is the meaning of this?! Did you
invite Marie here just to disparage her?
Not at all. I'm also laughing
at your pathetic state.
Coward. The old you would have punched me.
Marie is here!
And even the old me never
threw the first punch!
You're just afraid of me. After all, you've
never once beaten me in a sword fight,
you coward!
You never noticed that I was
letting you have the glory,
your highness?
Earlier, the arena was engulfed in cheers.
This time, let's stain it with screams.
Mark my words, I will make you
apologize for insulting Marie.
Wait, please!
Please mend things with him!
What Prince Luiphon said is true!
I can't blame anyone for saying
that I've sold myself.
I am foolish and timid, and I've always
done as my parents have told me.
But more than any of those things...
it's people ridiculing you because
of me that I cannot bear!
I'm sorry, I... I only
ever cause you trouble.
He only ridicules me out of
pity for my one-sided love.
I'm sure that he can't stand
seeing his rival brought so low.
Despite how he seems, he's a passionate man.
But... whatever his reasons, it doesn't
mean he's allowed to disparage you, Marie.
I will face him head on, defeat him,
and make him take it all back!
Thank you for being angry on my behalf.
But it's all right. I will
regain my honor myself!
More importantly for Prince Luiphon...
Lord Kyros, it's the fact that he called
you a coward that I want him to correct.
I found myself infuriated too.
Very well. Then, as one going into battle,
I ask for you to bestow a good luck kiss.
What?
Just a jest.
And now, I'll go pummel my
best friend into the ground.
R-Right.
And now...
we have the winner of the swordsmanship
contest, Count Kyros Granado,
and the third prince of the Kingdom
of Diltz, the captain of the knights,
his highness, Luiphon Sandhalkia Diltz,
in a special exhibition match!
You can do this, Lord Kyros.
Luiphon, put on your helmet.
You'll get gravely injured.
And you, dear Kyros.
If that noble nose of yours gets plucked
off, sweet Marie might finally hate you.
Put your helmet on.
Th-Then...
Begin!
It seems your skills haven't declined!
Neither have yours!
They seem equally matched
in strength, but...
I have you!
Lord Kyros, don't let him beat you!
That's an interesting move to make!
What? Is that allowed?!
Definitely not.
Winner! Count Kyros Granado!
Y-You did it! Lord Kyros!
SILENCE...
That fight was amazing!
I guess fists are good too.
He was amazing!
Marie!
Come down here!
D-Did you require something of me?
Th-This is so high up!
Don't worry, Marie.
Lord Kyros.
I will take this moment
to make an announcement!
I, Kyros Granado, and Lady Marie Shaderan,
a baron's daughter, are betrothed!
What?
Together, Lady Marie and I will
serve this kingdom to our utmost.
I swear it on the Granado name!
Betrothed? Lord Kyros?
Who is Baron Shaderan?
Marie.
Everyone wants to see your face.
B-But...
Everyone is expecting a beauty
the equal of Lord Kyros.
Someone like me will only embarrass him.
I'm scared.
It's all right. You are a far more
wonderful woman than you know.
And no matter what happens, I
will always be by your side.
You are beautiful!
There are so many things
that frighten me...
but if you will be here with me,
then perhaps I can overcome them.
Nice work! Congratulations!
How lovely!
Granado! Granado!
Excuse me.
Oh, you're the one from this afternoon!
Sorry that I couldn't stop the
prince's awful pranks.
Not at all. Please don't worry.
More importantly...
I'd love to join the peeling contest this time!
You sure are an odd one!
Here you are.
Thank you. I can't wait to test my skill.
What?
This seems like fun.
Lord Kyros?
May I try this with you?
Y-Yes.
You're very good.
I have to camp out for work sometimes.
How is Prince Luiphon?
In the prime of health.
That's your fault, Luiphon. You do one, too.
What?! Why do I have to?
Here.
Marie, are there any tricks to it?
Y-Yes!
First, you face the stem downwards,
then you rotate it sideways.
You're really good at this!
Yes, I'm quite good at peeling things.
After all, my life depended on leaving
as much of the edible parts as possible.
You're tougher than you seem. And
I love that part of you too!
Not really.
The woman doesn't even like you.
Is it fun being a clown who's
racing around, going nowhere?
Yes, it's fun.
Just having Marie with me makes
every day seem to sparkle.
Even if she doesn't love me, when I think
that tomorrow we may grow a little closer,
it's so much fun I can't stand it.
The day that we become a true married couple
may be years, or decades, in the future,
but I'm certain that I will have fun
showering Marie with love until I die.
Lord Kyros.
To be frank, that doesn't make you
the least bit dashing, dear Kyros.
I know.
Well, as long as you're satisfied...
then just do as you like.
E-Excuse me!
I want to know all about
Lord Kyros' good qualities!
What?
And so...
I hope you'll tell me lots
of stories again sometime!
I understand now, Your Highness.
You just wanted to talk about your
beloved best friend's best qualities.
That's why you invited me.
I'm sorry about before.
What is this?!
It's made for display, isn't it?
You should've noticed when you touched it!
Blast you! I am the third prince and
captain of our renowned knights!
One day I will have you both, husband and
wife, dragged off for insulting royalty!
I am so angry right now! Don't you
understand what lèse-majesté is?
Prince Luiphon is amusing, isn't he?
Yes. You'd never get tired of him, right?
Lady Marie, I have a message to deliver
to the master, so I will be staying here.
His valet Wolfgang will
accompany you in my stead.
Pleased to be of service, my lady.
I see.
Thank you for today, Marie.
No, thank you, Lord Kyros, for letting
me see such a dashing side of you.
The truth is, I'd never beaten
Luiphon in a sword bout before.
Lord Kyros, you are a truly strong person.
That's because you're with me, Marie.
Whatever you may wish, I will devote all
of myself to make that wish come true.
Because everything I am
now is thanks to you.
I'll see you back at the castle, Marie.
Yes.
Good night!
Coachman, please go now!
Marie! Wait, just now, you...
Please, wait!
In just two months from now...
I will marry the person my
sister was betrothed to.
It's a political marriage, but one
day, like a couple bound by love,
I hope we'll find happiness.
The two of us, together.
This does truly appear to be a
letter from the House of Shaderan.
Yes. The handwriting is correct as well.
Mio...
Are Baron Shaderan and his wife
really Marie's birth parents?
Toppo's cooking is the best in the world!
And I'll ply my skills again today!
My lady is in the midst of working hard
in preparation for the wedding ceremony.
Let Toppo's sublime sweets
soothe your heart and body!
Next time...
"Am I Enough As I Am?"
Episode 6 "Am I Enough As I Am?"
You'd like a second serving?
It would be my pleasure!